hamidashita kaze wo atsumete mitai na
I want to try and gather the unrestrained winds
nami no saki tsutatte kanata e kaketeku
I'll run toward the horizon alongside the wave crests
kakugo wa kimatteru
I've made my decision
michi wa tookutemo
even if there's a long way to go on that road
egaita mirai e tsudzuiteru
I'll continue towards the future I've planned
toki ga bokura wo sekashite kodou ga supiido agetetta
time rushes us, the heartbeat speeds up
yume no naka de mezametemo onaji hikari wo sagashita
when I woke in the middle of a dream, I kept searching for that same light
kagayaku hoshizora no shita kazoekirenai seiza to kage
under the shining star-lit sky, with countless constellations and shadows
sono saki ni kimi wa nani wo nani wo mitsumete iru darou
there was something beyond that, what were you gazing at?
nani wo mitsumete iru darou
what were you gazing at?
The Dark Cloud
Sneaks Up
Come... come... come...
The villagers are welcoming us.
Everyone seems to be safe.
It seems like the Kurosuki Family
ran away in fear.
Hey...
Here they come!
Naruto! Don't come...
If you value your life
be quiet.
Karashi...
I heard that you were deeply sorry
for your actions...!
How could I shamelessly
run back to the curry house?!
Now!
Did you see that?!
Although Master Raiga is not around
the Kurosuki Family is eternal!
Hey... what are you looking for?
Isn't it obvious? The brats!
Are you referring to us?
What?!
What you crushed were our forms
made by the Shadow Clone Jutsu
and the Transformation Jutsu.
Take formation!
Ninja Art: Black Tornado!
Wha...?
Those were also made by
the Shadow Clone Jutsu
and the Transformation Jutsu!
We saw through everything!
Here I go.
Leaf Hurricane!
Disperse!
Byakugan!
2 palms! 4 palms!
8 palms!
16 palms!
32 palms!
8 Trigrams 64 Palms!
Here I come!
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Clone Spinning Axe Kick!
Huh?! Oww...
It's already over...
What?! Not fair!
Man! You could've saved
some for me!
Just when I thought
I'd try the new Jutsu!
Gosh, you never learn do you!
Karashi, are you prepared?
I was just kidding!
How dare you torment us!
You really think
we'll let this slide as a joke?
I couldn't help it! If I didn't listen
I would have gotten killed
by the Kurosuki family.
In place of the Kurosuki family
I'll crack your head
with this hammer!
Yeah! Yeah!
I'm sorry...
Please move, Lee!
Please hit me until
you guys are satisfied.
Why you?
It's partly my responsibility
that the once kind-hearted Karashi
went and joined a gang.
Yours?
Because of me
he got the impression
that power is everything.
Right, that's right!
Though I knew that it's a bad thing
I just had to...
You be quiet!
Karashi is still inexperienced.
But he has skills to make curry
that can save people's lives.
Please give Karashi the opportunity
to make amends by making curry.
If Karashi goes astray again
then I will...!
Punish him with my fists!
Everyone what do you think
about letting Lee and Grandma Sansho
take care of this situation...
After all he was just
an underling of the Kurosuki family.
It's not like he directly
attacked us or anything...
Let's have Lee educate him harshly...
In that case...
Thank you very much!
Th-Thank you...
And with this our mission is complete.
No not yet...
Huh?
Are you all right?
What's the point of being all right?
I can't live alone.
Don't say that!
Why don't we just
leave this weakling!
Everyone has to live alone!
But don't you need friends
who can help you and stuff...?
I'm talking about some basics!
I hate people who are indecisive!
I was frail
from the time I was born.
That shabby cabin was
the entire world for me.
I have no memory of my parents...
I survived only by
the small amount of food
that the villagers sometimes
brought me...
But even someone like me
had a power that no one else did.
Here you go.
Thank you...
Is your leg okay?
The one you cut with the scythe?
D-Did I tell you that story?!
No... I kind of found out...
How? No one else besides me
came today or yesterday, right?
No, I just saw it from here...
Scary!
As time went by everyone began
to fear me since I had the power
to know what was happening outside
even from my room.
Did you know?!
I heard that Ranmaru has
the ability to see everything...
Were we being spied on every day?
Get out of the village!
You monster!
And so I had no more visitors...
All I could do was to wait to die.
That's when Raiga saved me...
I see. What a bitter past.
Yes, it is.
Hmm...
Raiga took me out to
the unknown world.
Ranmaru, try opening your eyes...
This is the outside world where
we'll be living from now on... okay?
Okay...
If Raiga isn't here
it's the same as losing my body.
Perhaps Raiga became known
as one of the Seven Ninja Swords
Men of the Mist
because he was able
to borrow your power.
It seems like you two
helped each other to live...
Yes.
That's not true!
You were being used for
Raiga's evil deeds!
I might have been... used...
But good or bad doesn't matter to me.
I'm just a sense organ...
Then that won't mean
that you're really living!
Huh?
See you have to do your best
to live from now on!
Firstly, eat the curry of life
and cheer up!
That's right!
You will get nourishment.
That will hurt the body instead,
wouldn't it?
Naruto, you can't eat it either, right?
Actually the more I eat it
the more energized my body feels...
That curry saved my life you know!
Until the day you're able
to walk alone
I will become your body!
Okay?
I have one favor to ask...
Huh...?
Byakugan!
As I expected...
I can no longer see life in Raiga.
Can you see Ranmaru?
Yes.
Is this okay?
Yes...
Let's go... Mission is complete.
Hey!
— What?
— That is...!
One, two, one, two.
Grandma Sansho!
What's all this ruckus?!
Dust will go into the curry.
L-Lee and the others came back!
K-Karashi is with them!
Is it worth the ruckus?
Grandma, aren't you happy?
One, two... One, two...
Your snot will go in!
Grandma Sansho! I'm back!
Karashi is here too!
M-Mom, sorry!
Please forgive me!
Please forgive him...
He says he'll devote himself
from now on
and train to take over
the Curry of Life Shop so please...
First you gotta eat...
Huh...
Wow, it looks good!
If you're not going to eat I will!
I've prepared some for each of you...
Oh my, that's a very pale child.
Yeah, can you prepare
some for him too?
Especially mild...
I prefer mild too...
Oh my...
Mom... thanks for the food!
It's a punishment times 300 curry...
It's spicy, it's spicy...
But it's good! It's good, Mom!
Here I have some for everybody!
It's okay, it's mild.
By the way you were part of
the Seven Ninja Swordsmen of
the Mist with Raiga, right?
Do you know a guy
named Zabuza?
Zabuza... you say?
Uh, then...
How about a guy with this huge sword
wrapped with something like a bandage
and has fish eyes?
Oh... that's Kisame...
Yeah, Kisame!
So do you know what
he's up to right now?
No... I heard that he slipped out
from the Mist Village.
I know his face but I don't know
anything beyond that.
I see...
Should I ask Grandma to
make you something else?
No, I don't need it...
I don't want to eat anything.
Thank you for your help...
Thank you very much.
Make a good village with everyone!
Um... where is Lee?
His mission still isn't complete.
Please wait Lee... I'm gonna die!
Okay, let's take a break here!
Let's do 300 push ups.
What?!
One, two... One, two...
300... all right.
It looks like...
there's going to be a storm.
Even if a real storm comes
it should be fine if we reinforce it
with these big trees!
Oh my, thanks for doing this.
No, it's our thanks for the curry.
Uh-uh.
But compared to you guys
my Karashi is...
Tenten? I'm worried about
Karashi and Ranmaru
whom we left behind
at the curry shop.
We're okay
so could you check on them there?
Karashi?!
Hey...
Is the Boss really still alive?
That Neji person didn't seem
to sense it then...
But I know.
Raiga...
Oh...
You were everything to me!
I was only waiting to die...
when you told me that
we'll live on together!
To me, being with you was living...
I won't hold a funeral for you either.
Even if it costs me my life
I won't let you die!
Ranmaru!
Did you die, Ranmaru?!
Karashi...?
dokomademo tsudzuku michi ni wa ironna koto arunda ne
so many things happen on this endless road, right?
tsuyogari na kimi ga kyou wa juwaki koshi ni namida koe
although you're strong-willed your voice wavered on the phone today
donna yume oikakete kokomade kitan darou
what dreams did you chase to get here?
wakara na kunattari suru koto wa boku ni datte aru kara nee BABY
even I have times when I just don't understand baby
kimi ga namida no toki ni wa boku ga soba ni iru kara
when you're sad I'll be close to you
hanareba nare no yoru datte boku wa soba ni iru kara
even on nights when we're apart I'll be close to you
boku wa soba ni iru kara
I'll be close to you
What?! Tenten fell off the cliff?!
Then we gotta go save her
right away!
Please calm down! Naruto!
Tenten can't be that clumsy.
Huh? But that's what Karashi said.
Unfortunately this might be
some kind of trap.
What? Trap?
Karashi...
Well didn't they get annihilated?
Next time:
"Raiga's Counterattack."